Prentiss Taylor
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Subject Files, 1885-1991, undated, Series 10:; (Box 3-21, OV 22; 18.0 linear feet; Reels 5913-5935)
  - Carl Van Vechten Booklets, undated and 1923-1930 (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 462-536)
  - Carl Van Vechten Programs, 1920-1950 (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 538-571)
  - Arthur and Gertrude Verner, 1948-1975 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 574-580)
  - Veterans Administration, 1959 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 582-584)
  - Ramond Vickers, 1932 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 586-591)
  - Victorian Society in America, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 593-646)
  - Margaret H. Vincent, 1962 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 648)
  - Virginia Commission for the Arts, 1980 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 650-655)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1956-1978, (3 folders) (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 657-797)
  - Virginia Printmakers, 1960 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 799-800)
  - Virginia State University, 1980 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 802-804)
  - University of Virginia, 1958-1983 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 806-844)
  - Donald Vogler, 1979 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 846)
  - Aline Fruhauf Vollmer and Erwin P. Vollmer, 1950-1986, (3 folders; included oversized materials from Box 21) (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 848-976)
  - Frederica Von Stade, 1973-1979 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 978-991)
  - Mary Heaton Vorse, 1966 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 993)
  - Monty W., 1964-1966 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 995-999)
  - Robert W. Wagner, 1964 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 1001-1002)
  - Gwendolyn Wagner, 1962-1966 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 1004-1008)
  - A'Lelia Walker, 1983 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 1010)
  - Alice Walker, 1978 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 1012-1013)
  - Eleanor S. Walker, 1965 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 1015-1016)
  - John Walker, 1965 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 1018-1019)
  - Wallace Haynes Walker and Isabella Brockway Walker, 1961-1983 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 1021-1056)
  - Lewis Wallace (autograph), 1885 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 1058-1061)
  - Arthur and May Gove Wallon, 1958-1973 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 1063-1072)
  - William Walter, 1977 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 1074)
  - Walters Art Gallery, 1937-1960 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 1076-1078)
  - Ty ? Wanamaker, 1969 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 1080)
  - Suen Chin Wang, undated (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 1082)
  - War Damage Corporation, 1945 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 1084-1088)
  - Lynd Ward, 1961-1985 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 1090-1105)
  - Virginia Ward, 1984 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 1107-1109)
  - Jessie and Heinz Warneke, undated (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 1111-1115)
  - George L. Warren, 1981 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 1117)
  - Ferol Sibley Warthen, 1958-1975 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 1119-1133)
  - Gerald Wartofsky, 1964-1984 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 1135-1138)
  - Washington International Center, 1958-1960 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 1140-1199)
  - Washington Opera, 1978 (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 1201)
  - Washington Print Club Bylaws, 1958-1987, (9 folders) (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 1204-1210)
  - Washington Print Club Membership Lists, 1958-1987, (9 folders) (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 1212-1266)
  - Washington Print Club Minutes of Board Meetings, 1981-1986, (9 folders) (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 1268-1412)
  - Washington Print Club Correspondence, undated and 1965-1986, (9 folders) (Box 19, Reel 5933, Frame 1414-1432)
  - Washington Print Club Correspondence, undated and 1965-1986, (31 folders) (Box 19, Reel 5934, Frame 13-256)
  - Washington Print Club Newsletter Committee Notes, 1981-1982, (31 folders) (Box 19, Reel 5934, Frame 258-309)
  - Washington Print Club Drafts of Newsletter Articles, 1958-1987, (31 folders) (Box 19, Reel 5934, Frame 311-423)
  - Washington Print Club, Washington Print Club Newsletter, 1973-1987, (31 folders) (Box 19, Reel 5934, Frame 425-1057)
  - Washington Print Club, Washington Print Club Newsletter, 1973-1987, (31 folders) (Box 20, Reel 5934, Frame 1059-1120)
  - Washington Print Club Print Council of America Newsletter, 1958-1959, (5 folders) (Box 20, Reel 5934, Frame 1121-1169)
  - Washington Print Club Clippings and Miscellaneous Printer Material, 1958-1987, (5 folders) (Box 20, Reel 5934, Frame 1171-1185)
  - Washington Project for the Arts, 1988-1989 (Box 20, Reel 5934, Frame 1187-1188)
  - Washington School of Psychiatry, 1958 (Box 20, Reel 5934, Frame 1190)
  - Washington Water Color Club/Washington Water Color Association Constitution, 1944-1959, (2 folders) (Box 20, Reel 5934, Frame 1193-1203)
  - Washington Water Color Club/Washington Water Color Association Membership Lists, 1956-1967, (2 folders) (Box 20, Reel 5934, Frame 1205-1235)
  - Washington Water Color Club/Washington Water Color Association Correspondence, 1943-1973, (8 folders) (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1250-1285)
  - Washington Water Color Club/Washington Water Color Association Clippings and Newsletters, 1942-1986, (8 folders) (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1287-1331)
  - Washington Water Color Club/Washington Water Color Association Exhibition Catalogs and Prospect uses, 1937-1973, (8 folders) (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1333-1438)
  - Susie B. Waters, undated (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1440-1441)
  - Watkins Gallery, 1969-1975 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1443-1451)
  - Forbes and Nan Watson, 1963-1966 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1453-1459)
  - Margaret Ann Watts, 1965 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1461-1462)
  - June Wayne, 1957-1973, (4 folders) (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1464-1529)
  - Elizabeth Weaver, 1969 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1531)
  - Eleanor Wedd, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1533-1547)
  - Reynold H. Weidenaar, 1965-1975 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1549-1560)
  - Charles Weidman, 1975 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1562-1564)
  - Anita Weiner, 1964 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1566)
  - Milton Weingarten, 1973-1978 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1568-1569)
  - James Lesesne Wells, 1961-1980, (2 folders) (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1571-1596)
  - Michael Welzenbach, 1990 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1598-1603)
  - Stow Wengenroth, 1960-1982, (2 folders) (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1605-1649)
  - Volkmar Kurt Wentzel, 1961 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1651-1654)
  - Westinghouse Corps. Nuclear Center, 1973 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1656-1657)
  - E. Weyhe Gallery, 1938-1976 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1659-1673)
  - The Wharf Players of Provincetown, 1925 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1675)
  - Virginia Scates Wharton, 1960 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1677)
  - Rozelle Whelan, 1979 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1679-1681)
  - A. C. White Transfer and Storage Company, 1959 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1683-1684)
  - Elizabeth Wade White, 1954-1975 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1686-1719)
  - Wade White, 1956-1990 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1721-1747)
  - Donald Whitehill, 1951 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1749-1750)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1958-1979 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1752-1758)
  - Gertrude Clarke Whittall, 1963 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1760)
  - Who's Who in American Art, 1966-1968 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1762-1764)
  - Who's Who Among Black Americans, 1975-1976 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1766-1768)
  - Whyte Bookshop, 1953 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1770)
  - James, Orrin, and Polly Whyte, undated (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1772-1773)
  - Barbara Wickham, 1959 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1775-1776)
  - Paul Raysor Wignall, 1984 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1778-1779)
  - Philip E. Wilcox, 1929-1932, (4 folders) (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1781-1839)
  - Emma L. Wilder, 1961-1967 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1841-1849)
  - Thornton Wilder, 1962 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1851)
  - Wilderness Society, 1960 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1853-1855)
  - Geneva Williams, 1969-1974 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1857-1860)
  - Gil and Deborah Williams, 1961-1985 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1862-1897)
  - Susan Williams, 1977 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1899-1900)
  - Sarah Wilson, 1957-1959 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1902-1907)
  - Marcella Comes Winslow, 1957-1976 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1909-1911)
  - The Winter Wheat Press, Washington, D.C., 1928-1953, (9 folders) (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 1913-2136)
  - Edna Wisenell?, 1958 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2138-2141)
  - Dick Wiser, 1986 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2143-2145)
  - Emily Harrold Withers, 1982 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2147)
  - Georgianna E. Wohlfert, 1981 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2149)
  - Woltz Studio, 1958 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2151)
  - Woman's National Democratic Club, 1978 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2153-2155)
  - Janet Woods, undated (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2157-2168)
  - Bill Woodward, 1958 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2170-2171)
  - Harold Wortham, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2173-2177)
  - Marjorie Worthington, 1976 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2179)
  - Thomas Wragg, 1985 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2181)
  - Crawford K. Wright, 1972 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2183)
  - Wright Designs and Associates, 1985 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2185)
  - Frank Wright, 1965-1981 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2187-2189)
  - Isabel Wunderlich, 1961 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2191-2193)
  - Gertrude Wyckoff, 1976 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2195-2197)
  - William Wynne, undated (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2199)
  - Yaddo, 1976 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2201-2203)
  - Yale University Art Gallery, 1979 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2205)
  - Yale University Library, 1952-1986, (4 folders) (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2207-2276)
  - Yoki B. Yamashita, 1963-1965 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2278-2281)
  - Tom R. Yanosky, 1973 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2283-2284)
  - Karel Yasko, 1982 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2286)
  - Leon Yochelson, 1982 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2288)
  - C. M. Young, 1957 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2290-2291)
  - William H. Young, Jr. and Mitzie Young, 1960-1979 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2293-2324)
  - Blanche Yurka, 1974 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2326)
  - Y.W.C.A., 1958-1968, (3 folders) (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2328-2401)
  - Alice Zahniser, 1964 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2403-2406)
  - John Zeigler, 1964 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2408-2409)
  - Maria Zerega, undated (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2411-2414)
  - Fay Zetlin, 1958-1982, (4 folders) (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2416-2483)
  - Carl and Laura Zigrosser, 1937-1985, (3 folders) (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2485-2534)
  - Zinn's, Ltd., 1961-1979, (2 folders) (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2536-2579)
  - William Zorach, 1966 (Box 20, Reel 5935, Frame 2581-2582)
  - Oversized lithograph printed on a handkerchief from the file of John English, (scanned with box 8, reel 5919, frames 956-980) (Box 21 (sol))
  - Oversized layout sheets for The Golden Stair Broadsides, Nos. 2-4, written by Langston Hughes and illustrated by Prentiss Taylor, (scanned with box 9, reel 5921, frames 707-1310) (Box 21 (sol))
  - Oversized drawings of patients at St. Elizabeth's Hospital by Prentiss Taylor, 1947, undated, (scanned with boxes 14-15, reels 5928, frames 728-1370 and reel 5929, frames 13-634) (Box 21 (sol))
  - Oversized photograph of the Ninth Annual Banquet of the Medical Society of St. Elizabeth's Hospital, 1946, (scanned with boxes 14-15, reels 5928, frames 728-1370 and reel 5929, frames 13-634) (Box 21 (sol))
  - Oversized drawing of Prentiss Taylor by Aline Fruhauf Vollmer Oversized Matted Photograph, Self Portrait of Carl Van Vechten, 1932, (scanned with boxes 14-15, reels 5928, frames 728-1370 and reel 5929, frames 13-634) (Box 21 (sol))
  - Oversized drawing of patients at St. Elizabeth's Hospital by Prentiss Taylor, undated, (scanned with boxes 14-15, reels 5928, frames 728-1370 and reel 5929, frames 13-634) (Box OV 22)
  - Oversized sheet of paper containing the writings of a patient from St. Elizabeth's Hospital, 1947, (scanned with boxes 14-15, reels 5928, frames 728-1370 and reel 5929, frames 13-634) (Box OV 22)
  - Oversized photograph of an unidentified banquet at St. Elizabeth's Hospital, undated, (scanned with boxes 14-15, reels 5928, frames 728-1370 and reel 5929, frames 13-634) (Box OV 22)
  - Oversized photograph of the Fourteenth Annual Banquet of the Medical Society of St. Elizabeth's Hospital, 1951, (scanned with boxes 14-15, reels 5928, frames 728-1370 and reel 5929, frames 13-634) (Box OV 22)